Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his triumphs, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
We're in the glamour world now. In this place, the impossible becomes real.
Vanessa, Sally, Magna, Luck, and Charmy had been taken to a world of fantasy where they matched wits with Dorothy's elven form.
Combo spell! Flame, lightning, exploding!
Working together, the team managed to defeat her and escape the treacherous glamour world.
Combo spell, reflect Iris.
Why can't I move?
We're stuck!
There's no hope for you. Now die, helpless worms.
Meanwhile, Asta and the other Black Bulls were fighting a possessed Ghosh and Marie when Henry attempted a risky move.
Now...
It's your turn!
You're not even close to done, Henry! Don't die!
I don't want to die. I want to live on with my friends.
Please don't go. We'll miss you.
Get one of those a single one of my friends!
That's Ghosh for you, too!
Do you hear me, Ghosh?!
That's enough. Give those bodies back to Ghosh and Marie right now.
Asta was able to expel the elven spirits from Ghosh and Marie, and the two returned to normal.
Thanks for saving us, bunch of jerks.
All right! The rest of the Black Bulls are back together!
Once we recharge, we'll go help the captain!
Yeah!
All right.
Let's!
止まんない衝動
とんでもなれ
やんぬいがないんでしょう
分かり合えない場所を
やり切るまで染められる
風の世界生きる
全て無くなるまでやるよ
Let's!
Ah!
This must be the Shadow Palace
You know what that is?
Yes I do
An ancient spatial magic construct
Who would have guessed that it actually existed?
Rumor has it if you can make it inside
You'll find all manner of powerful magic items
And priceless treasures free for the taking
So what's our strategy going to be?
That's a good question
Eat up!
Don't let a single crumb go to waste!
Ah!
Captain Yami the Mansons guy already went in
But I bet there are some super tough enemies in there
So let's make sure we're nice and nourished
Before we go help them
Chill down people!
Here Marie
Ready?
Uh
Um
Could you please not do that?
There's no need to be shy around me
My darling goddess
Uh
I told you to cut it out
Have a bite Ghosh
There's no need to be shy around me either
Uh
Ah
Yes my beautiful magic is being replenished bit by impeccable bits
This is great!
That healing magic of yours made me good as new!
Thank you so much Mimosa!
Don't worry about it I'm just happy I could be of some help
Now I'll be able to bust out my dark form again!
Here you'd better eat something too
Thanks I appreciate it
Typical Asta
You always overdo it
I swear you'd be hopeless without me here to help you
I mean you're still hopeless whether I'm around or not
So you'd better not read into that
I can't help but read into it
Huh?
Asta!
Make sure you take good care of that unique body
Hey wait a second why are you wearing his clothes?
Why is it a big deal?
Oh yeah hers got kinda ripped so I let her borrow mine
And how exactly did that happen?
Whatever just tell me why you're all buddy-buddying with one of our worst enemies
You're asking me this now?
Because Asta promised me that if I fought on your side he would let me do whatever I want to his body after the big battle's over
Whoa whoa
Excuse me?
Do whatever you want
That wasn't what I said at all
Eh close enough
I promise you I'll use anesthesia
Well you know
What's wrong with you Asta?
She's our enemy
You're so stupid
What
I don't know what's going on between you two but please step aside so I can heal him
I thought you already finished doing that
You're unbelievable
Take that
Oh come on
I hate to interrupt you but don't you think you should eat something too so your mana comes back
Did I ask for your opinion?
Hey I outrank you
And on royalty
That's all that matters
I'm still your superior
What's the matter?
They're here
I see too
Scutcher now
You're dead
I see you're awake
About time
Sorry to keep you waiting dear sister
They're here
Captain Foygolion and Captain Merleona
Wow Captain Merleona
Wow Captain Foygolion
You didn't die or anything
That's awesome
And you've got salamander too
Yes Asta
It would appear that you've gotten much stronger during my slumber
You knew it
I'm totally buff
And Captain Merleona
Were you supposed to rest for at least one more day?
Don't need to
I'm not weak
Yeah but
That woman is unstoppable
So they're finally back in the fray
Took them long enough
Orton your cell is amazing
I can't believe he's already recovered from such a serious injury
Am I late?
I'm sorry
Huh
Then try to make up for it in battle
Even with salamander's help
You won't outdo me
Hey guys
Look
Am I seeing things here?
Or is that hole getting smaller?
You're right it is
We should hurry
When we place the final magic stone into its pedestal inside the palace
The elves great reincarnation will be complete
A core surprise must be paid for our use of these bodies
Sadly
Their human souls will be sent to the underworld
There's not much time
You will pay for your insolence
I'll see to that
Golden Dawn's best guys
We can't catch a break
While my gorgeousness has no limits
Unfortunately my magic has a maximum and I've just about reached it
We need to move
But
With these numbers
I say the captains go inside
Let the black bulls take care of everything here on the ground
With my thread magic and Charmy's cooking we'll all be fine
You can count on us
Hey Asta
You should go in with them
They're gonna need your sword if they have to change somebody back don't you think
Okay I'll go
Do your best black bulls
Roger
Some of these bozos down here still think they're elves though so try to make it quick alright
You got it
Wait I'll go in with you Asta
They'll also need someone who can heal
Go with them Mimosa
Don't worry I'll provide my beautiful support to our comrades here
Okay
That way I can protect Asta
My brother actually said something smart for once
But wait I can-
No Elf!
Is that solid?
You go too!
I hate to say this
But for right now
You're stronger than me
So enjoy it while you can because I will surpass you again
I'm your older brother
I have to
Now hurry
And make certain you come back
Remember
Our family's pride is at stake
Understood
I promise I'll come back
Thank you solid
Well then shall we?
Don't fall behind us
Well?
You won't get past us!
You're in their way!
exposure
Here we go
In to the Shadow Palace
ル a
This is freaky!
Oh boy, here we go!
Why are we floating?
I assume this is a way of dealing with intruders.
This mana we're swimming in certainly is unusual.
I can't control my magic in here!
The Shadow Palace. I hear it's the boundary between this world and the next.
Are we gonna die?
Why are you trying to be funny because I am not laughing?
Just shut up!
I refuse to die!
Wait!
Are you hurt, Osta?
Oh my gosh, I'm so sorry!
Don't worry, I'll heal you right away!
Plant recovery magic!
Princess healing flower robe!
So we're inside the palace now?
Where did everyone else go?
Sweet, I'm healed up!
It's almost like nothing ever happened!
Thanks, Mimosa!
Now we'll use magic flower guideposts to figure out what the layout of this place is like.
Wow! You really know your stuff, don't you?
Let me see.
It looks like there are several big spaces.
And I sense Elven Mana in each of them.
We're in one of the many connecting chambers that run throughout the palace.
And apparently the rest of our team's been scattered across multiple areas.
So before we can regroup, they'll have to defeat all the Elves.
And that won't be easy.
We're up against the Apostles of Sephira.
Yeah. One of their members alone has more magic than a squad captain.
The uppermost chamber seems to have the strongest magic of all.
Bet that's him.
Okay!
So once everybody defeats the Elf who's waiting inside each room, we meet up where the boss is!
Right!
And the central chamber is directly above our heads.
We should go!
Yeah!
I don't know who we're gonna have to go up against.
But our only option is to win!
Don't tell me!
These paintings...
Hey there.
You and I have met before.
It's real.
Oh, come on! We went over this last time! My name's Lyra!
Oh, well.
I'm waiting for the final magic stone to arrive.
So in the meantime, I say we practice a little bit.
How's that sound?
Here's an idea!
How about I wake you up right now?
I'm already as awake as I can be.
So there's no need.
Picture magic is fun, huh?
It took a little while to get used to.
But it's way better than the scribbles I did before.
We elves are about to design a totally new world!
And as soon as we get rid of all you ugly humans, we'll have a nice fresh canvas to paint on!
Fine, then. Looks like we're gonna have to do this the hard way.
I don't get it.
Where did everybody go?
I need some backup!
Sounds like you're lonely, so I'll play with you.
But I have a feeling the game won't go on very long.
You again?
I don't understand this. Why are you here?
Aw, poor thing. You look so confused.
I may be Fauna, but I'm a much different Fauna than the one you remember.
So you're the opponent I wound up with.
You may be a filthy royal, but at least your mana is interesting.
I'm about to teach you the importance of respecting your elders, you mangy brat!
Despite my adolescent form, I won't be easy prey.
No human alive can tame this beast.
I heard that you had become a captain.
Yet we meet again to fight on opposing sides.
How regrettable.
You were once a great man, Lord Kaiser.
I suppose there's no reason for you to hold back, seeing as you and I don't actually know one another.
Indeed. I won't hold back. That would be ignoble.
And what's more, I know Lord Kaiser is more than capable of putting up a decent fight.
He never cared much for the spotlight, so I assume he became the captain of the Purple Orcas for the sake of his squad.
His poor wife was terribly worried about him.
He's an excellent magic knight, and there are people awaiting his return.
So you will surrender him now!
Flame Spirit Magic, Salamander Spirit!
Ha ha ha! That's quite a powerful spell you have.
Sadly, it will never reach me.
Lord Kaiser's Vortex Magic allows him to deflect and disperse opposing attacks.
That, combined with the Elven magic, makes him impervious to Salamander's power.
None of my spells will harm him.
He can use the Vortex for offense as well.
Even with Monoskin, I'm taking a great deal of damage.
And all the while, he's washing my magic away.
No!
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Ha ha ha ha!
I burned you to a crisp and you're still fighting!
Speed, reflexes, and strength!
A worthy foe.
Impressive!
For a mere boy!
Same goes for you!
I never knew of another human that could put up a decent fight!
It's been a while since I had this much fun fighting a snot-nosed brat one-on-one!
It takes me back to my youth!
He detects magic and blocks it automatically, so my attacks will never touch him!
This unfair advantage...
It reminds me of my sister.
She's had that wild, audacious spirit all her life.
I idolized her for her strength.
That is, until I became frustrated with her devil-may-care attitude.
There you are!
I'll get you this time!
Come back inside!
It's time for our training with Sister Teresa!
Hey!
Just let her go, Fueko.
Mero doesn't need to train with us.
She'll become stronger on her own.
That's how special she is.
Looking back now, I'm sure I must have been quite jealous of her.
What?! I don't believe this!
You really have no interest in working with the Crimson Lion Kings.
That's right.
But why is that?
With amazing abilities like yours, you'd be unstoppable as a magic knight.
You could even become the Wizard King someday!
After I get my Grimoire tomorrow, I'm setting off to explore the strong magic regions.
Who'd want to waste their time on guard duty and catching petty criminals?
It's foolish.
Foolish?
Sister!
Hmm?
I want to spar.
One round, both of us giving it our all.
Right here and now.
Hmph.
Oh, really?
At least make it fun for me this time.
You're so dull.
This momentous fight between the Vermillion family's eldest son and eldest daughter would
later come to be regarded as the Tuesday of blood and blagues.
That overly serious fool was on fire back then!
You're probably the most powerful human in this whole kingdom!
I'm sure if I can defeat you, the rest of the humans will be no trouble at all.
Be gone!
You're mine, human!
Not me!
She's unorthodox, cavalier, and even somewhat mad!
But everywhere she goes, people clear a path, fearing her bold power!
She's overbearing, unbending, and most of all, boring!
But his refined, exceptional strength has earned him the respect and loyalty of all who follow him!
My sister!
My brother!
He's worthy of being called the strongest!
Reignition!
Time's two!
He erased his magic using Salamander as a decoy.
That's how he was able to permeate the vortex and get close enough to hit me!
By using willpower to endure my attacks, she conserved enough magic for her next strike.
As my sister's younger brother!
As that idiot's older sister!
I must prevail!
I have to be strong!
Oh
Thank you.